WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
sync and corrections by solfieri
www.MY-SUBS.com
- Hey.
- Welcome.
Sawatdee khrap.
The mysterious Steve. I'm Sritala.
Yes, you are. Great to meet you.
Such a fan. Thank you for having us.
And this is my husband, Khun Jim.
How are you?
Hello, sir. How are you?
I thought we'd sit up on the terrace.
This way.
Magnificent house you have here.
Thank you.
How long have you lived in Thailand?
First came here in '62.
Jim just got out of the hospital.
Would you like a drink?
Oh, I'd love a...
Just a tea, an herbal tea.
Would that be okay?
Uh, whiskey. If you have it,
I'd love a whiskey.
Big-time movie director, huh?
Well...
What have you directed, may I ask?
Uh, what haven't I directed?
You know what I mean?
Mostly action films. Uh...
The... The Enforcer.
Uh... The Executor.
The Notary.
That was a trilogy.
I just watch whatever she has on.
Is that right?
There's an actress
from one of the shows we watch
staying, right now,
at our hotel in Samui.
Jaclyn Lemon. Do you know her?
Oh, yeah, not well.
But we're in the same business,
you know? Small world.
What kind of movie are you making here?
You know what? It's a fun caper.
Like a thriller. It's got... everything.
Uh, killings, double-crossings, um...
action, all the stuff that people like.
And what would be my role?
She is a former prostitute,
now a madam,
and she owns a popular bordello.
Um... the producer told me that...
the part would be based on me.
That's why you wanted to come here,
to get to know me.
- Yeah, you know, I...
- A prostitute?
Um... No, I think he meant
she's very formidable because she knows
all the secrets of all
the most powerful men
in Thailand. She's... She's tough.
She's brilliant.
A knockout, obviously.
And she sings.
She sings?
It's one of my favorite parts
of the movie.
Yeah, should have led
with that one. Um, thank you.
You know what? Goddamn it.
I think I might have a drink after all.
Could I get a whiskey, darling?
That mi... That might be helpful.
Uh, I don't think... one wouldn't hurt.
My kind of drinker.
Remember this.
Every one of us
has the capacity to kill.
Buddhist scripture
condemns violence in every form.
Violence, aggression, anger
stem from same source.
Fear.
The only good faith response
is to sit with your feelings.
Violence does spiritual harm
to victim and to perpetrator.
Buddhists believe always nonviolence.
Do you know whose party it is?
Yeah, it's Chloe's party.
Who's Chloe?
Mom, you met her.
It's Gary's girlfriend.
Oh, no. Not the boat people.
Look, you guys don't need to come.
All right? I'm... I'm just
passing along the invites.
You know what? I'm all dolled up.
Let's go. If only I could find my purse.
Oh, God. The boat people.
Okay.
- If we're gonna go, let's go.
- Yeah.
Come on. Let's go.
Mom.
What does he want from me?
Let's go find out.
I mean, aren't you curious?
Look, if you don't go tonight,
he's just gonna come looking
for you again.
I say we just get it over with.
He knows I know.
Mom, he's not gonna do anything
to you, all right?
'Cause I'll be there.
Let's just go see what he has to say.
Aren't you jet-lagged?
No, but I'm hungry. Let's go.
- Good evening.
- Hi.
- Three for dinner?
- Uh, yes. Yes.
How are you?
Oh, I have a lot of feelings.
- I like your shirt.
- Oh, thank you.
Anything from the bar?
- I'll have a glass of rosé.
- Same.
A... A bottle, perhaps?
Definitely.
Just to let you know,
I'll be the entertainment for tonight.
- Ooh.
- I do hope you enjoy.
Any advice from a professional
to overcome stage fright?
Just go for it. Yeah.
I'm sure you'll be great. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck that.
Where's that rosé?
Thank you.
Uh... What's your name? You're lovely.
Your producer says you've been watching
some of my films.
- I'm sorry?
- Which films did you watch?
Some are better than others.
Uh, the ones I saw, you were fantastic.
Just terrific.
How do you know?
What do you mean?
Well, they are entirely in Thai.
Well, I'm a director.
I'm more visual anyway.
So, which one did you watch?
The titles are hard to remember.
Hey, I'm... I'm gonna need
another one of these, I think.
Well, just tell me one of the plots.
Um, you were, uh, royalty or something.
A queen, maybe?
Is that... Is that right?
That's the one.
You know what?
I... I have a... I have a thought.
I would really love
to hear about
how you conquered Thailand.
Maybe you and I could speak
in another room.
That way, your wife and Frank here
- can really connect.
- Steve.
Steve. I'm... Steve, I'm sorry.
Frank is a director
that I'm working with
- on this other project.
- He's a busy guy.
Anyway, listen, I just want you guys
to have an opportunity
to bond as artists.
And... maybe I can pick
your brain about what it's like
to do business in Thailand.
I mean, you've been very successful.
Sure.
Let's take it to the den.
Hey, you made it.
- Hey.
- How are you?
Where's your brother?
He's at some Buddhist temple thing
with my sister.
Oh, cool.
It's a cult.
Wh... Where's the bar?
It's over here. I'll show you.
Oh, hey, you two.
- Friendly face.
- Hi.
I'm sorry. What are your names again?
I'll take a large whiskey,
- with a little ice.
- Timothy.
Can I have a G&T, please? Thank you.
Yeah!
And a gin and tonic.
- Yo.
- Hey.
You know, these guys
must know the only reason
they have these hot girlfriends
is 'cause they're loaded.
That's gonna be you in 30 years.
Why are you so mean to me?
I'm not trying to be mean.
But that's what you give off.
And you're dating some old,
bald dude with a bunch of money.
How's that any different?
No, it's not the same.
That's not the reason I'm with him.
Then what's the appeal?
The first day we met,
he told me his whole life story,
and I just knew
we were meant to be together.
See, you can't even go there.
He has this sadness.
It really touches me.
I want to heal him.
It's like we're in
this yin and yang battle.
And I'm hope...
and Rick is pain.
And, eventually, one of us will win.
I need to call him.
Can you give me a sec?
Okay.
Your call
has been forwarded to voicemail.
The person you're trying to reach...
There's a monk down at the beach.
He has a meditation center.
I forget his name.
You ever met him?
No.
Seems like the real deal.
Dad, can I talk with you for a second?
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
Thank you.
Seems you've had quite a life.
Yeah, Thailand's been good to me.
But have you been good to Thailand?
I'd say so.
Some may disagree.
Well, you wanna make an omelet,
you gotta crack a few eggs.
Am I right?
This is a great country.
And back then, not much red tape.
You hit a roadblock,
you had a lot of options.
And if somebody got in your way?
Made your life difficult?
Lots of ways to take care of that.
I'm more careful now.
Got more to lose.
That's how life works.
When you're young,
you want to be king of the hill.
Then you get to be king of the hill,
and you miss it when you were young
and hungry and could...
swing free.
You know, someone once said
that the secret to life
is knowing...
when to stop.
I'm not sure how that follows.
Hmm.
Um, good evening.
Um, this is, um, a little song I wrote
when I was feeling a bit homesick.
How home may be cold and... and dirty.
But still, it is home.
I think we should go
to the Muay Thai thing.
- Mm.
- What?
I'm pretty tired.
Oh, right, I bet.
Laurie, why are you so bothered?
Just makes me not trust you,
to be honest.
Give me a break.
Like you're in love
with Valentin or something?
- No.
- Right.
So stop busting my balls.
I agree. It's not that big of a deal.
Was it a big deal when she did
the same thing with Dave?
With Dave?
At my wedding, she was all over Dave.
I'm sure you remember.
I was not.
And that was like 15 years ago.
Wait, what?
What is really going on with you?
If you're not happy
with your life, just own it.
Don't project and make mountains
out of molehills.
What's that supposed to mean?
If you're not happy
with your life, Laurie,
I don't know. Fucking change it.
I mean, I get what she's saying.
It's like...
you're not upset because of Valentin.
Yeah, I'm upset because of Jaclyn.
But are you?
You could've hooked up
with Valentin if you wanted,
but you chose not to.
Right? You chose to work at that company
your whole career,
and you chose to marry Brian.
If you always choose
the short stick, is it bad luck?
Are you life's victim?
Or are you doing it to yourself?
I mean, you know, when you know
someone long enough,
you do start to see certain patterns.
Okay. And what is that pattern, Kate?
Well, it's like,
the source of
your disappointment changes...
but the constant
is you're always disappointed.
Okay.
And you're always fake
and fronting like your life is perfect.
And you're vain and selfish.
You did something fucked up,
and I'm the one that has a problem?
Okay.
I'm gonna go to the fight
'cause why not? hmm?
You guys have a good night.
You're such a darling girl.
You're young. You're beautiful.
Why are you
with this middle-aged weirdo?
Does he have a lot of money?
You can't ask that.
Come to North Carolina.
I could introduce you
to some respectable men.
They would eat you up.
I actually love Rupert.
Are you scared of him?
I could get you out of this.
I'm glad you made it.
Hello.
Uh, how are you?
Do you wanna maybe go
inside the house? We could talk.
Well, uh, um, I was... I wanted
my son to come with me.
Oh, no, I'd prefer it was just us.
It... It won't take long.
If he doesn't see me,
he'll come looking.
I'm just gonna take
a couple minutes of your time,
and then I'll bring you
right back out to the party.
I mean, I... I had a few drinks.
No, no, no, not the drinks.
What's going on with you?
Look, if there's something
going on at work or something,
just tell me.
I mean, maybe I can help you.
You can't... You can't help.
Look, at this point, my career
is totally tied to yours.
So, if something bad is happening,
it's happening to both of us.
And I'll always be seen by everyone
as Timothy Ratliff's son,
and I'm okay with that.
I am, as long as everything
at work is going good.
And everything at work
is going good, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, Dad, I don't have
anything else but this.
I don't have any interests,
I don't have any hobbies, okay?
If I'm not a success, then I'm nothing.
And I can't handle being nothing.
I've put my whole life into this basket.
Into your basket, Dad.
So, if something's up, just...
What? Is something up?
Saxon...
nothing's up.
Kid, we're all good.
It's a party. You get out there
and enjoy yourself. All right?
So...
You know who I am.
And I'm sure you also know
something very tragic
happened to my wife, Tanya.
I had nothing to do with it, just...
to make that clear.
But it was getting
very complicated back home
and I just didn't want to spend
the rest of my life
dealing with legal shit and lawyers
and people making assumptions.
I love Thailand. I love the people.
Bought this house.
I'm happy.
I want to live
the rest of my life right here.
And I just...
don't wanna have any more headaches
if I can help it.
Tanya talked about you...
a lot.
She always felt guilty that
she didn't start that business with you.
And I know that she'd want you
to have some money to do that.
So...
I'm gonna give you 100,000 dollars.
Tanya would've wanted that.
And I know that she would
also want me to spend
the rest of my years in peace.
Maybe in exchange...
you could honor that.
That's, um...
very generous of you.
But, uh...
I need to think about it.
Okay, sure.
Sleep on it.
I'm not looking to make problems
for you. I...
I just... You know,
I need to sleep on it.
Is... Is that okay?
Sure.
- Hey.
- Hey. Where you been?
- I been looking all over for you.
- Let's go.
What, you're not gonna eat?
I mean, I just got all this...
Zion! I am not playing.
I want to get the fuck up out of here.
Okay, yeah. All right.
So, you got any kids?
Yeah, Sritala and I have got
a couple of daughters.
One of 'em lives in New York.
Other one lives here.
I bet they had a happy childhood
growing up here.
Yeah. You bet. Spoiled rotten.
Well, that's good 'cause...
if you don't have a happy childhood,
you don't have much, right?
Where are you? Which one's you?
That's you? Right there?
You're the one with the rhinestones?
- Yes! Yes.
- Oh my God!
I was 25 here.
Wow. Stunning.
- You still are.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- You sweet talker.
- I'm a truth-sayer, darling.
- Thank you.
You know, I've always wanted
to meet you.
That right?
The very first time I heard your name,
I was ten years old.
When my mother...
was dying.
How about that?
You've lost me.
I have...
fantasized...
about this moment a thousand times.
What is this?
Gloria Hatchett.
Name ring a bell?
Well, it seems like you should remember.
She had a husband.
You had him killed over some land deal,
or some shit.
You... You don't fucking remember that?
- He was my father.
- Gloria Hatchett?
He was a good man.
And I never got to meet him
because you're a fucking piece of shit.
Whoa.
Shut the fuck up.
I mean, it's like MC Hammer, Peter Pan.
It's got a little, um, Pippin.
It's the folk music and the rap music.
- Ah.
- Yeah.
You ruined my fucking life.
You may not remember him,
but you sure as fuck
are gonna remember me.
You motherfucker.
What's going on there?
Uh, these are all my dancers.
- I taught them all.
- Wow. Incredible. Look at that.
Hey, hey.
- We gotta go.
- Oh, yeah.
You are absolutely iconic.
Let's keep talking.
I got your number. You got my number?
Let's keep...
Let's keep chatting about this.
I feel really good about it.
Old man fell. Better help him.
Go, go. Go, go, go, go.
Come on, let's go, let's go, let's go!
Go! Come on, let's go!
Ah.
Mm.
- Laurie!
- Hi!
Three times. You learn, huh?
Oi!
- Hey.
I was hoping I would see you again.
- Yeah?
- Mm.
- Well, here I am.
- Mm. With great hair, huh?
I noticed. What is this? You want some?
Yeah.
Yeah!
Yes! Come on!
Huh?
- Hey.
So, what do you think?
Yeah, I... I think he's...
I think he's cool.
Yeah?
Like, I... I like that he's all about...
how to be the best person you can be,
and... and how to go through life
without making shit worse
for other people.
And I... I don't want to give in
to my dark shit.
You know, I don't want
to make things worse.
You're the best.
I love you.
I was actually thinking, just now,
I want to do it, too.
What? Do what?
Like, come with you. Here.
- What?
- Like, I'll take a gap year.
I mean, right now, I really...
I really don't feel like
going home.
Like, ever.
And, yeah, I...
I just think it'd be cool
to be somewhere else...
with you. You know?
Here.
Um, are you serious?
I... I thought you'd be excited.
No, I just, um...
I don't know.
Well, I better go back to my room.
Just wanted to see if you're okay.
See you in the morning.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Are you guys having fun?
Yep.
Yeah, but I think I might go.
Yeah, I'm really tired from last night.
Oh.
Well, I'll walk you back.
Oh, no, don't go.
Gary wants you to stay.
We had a long talk,
and it was really, um...
Yeah, it was good.
That's really good.
He finally opened up about his ex-wife.
Apparently, they never had sex.
And because she was so insecure,
he couldn't really tell her
what he was really into.
You know, like, sexually.
And he doesn't want that happening to us
because he loves me.
So, wait, what... what's he into?
Well, um, okay.
He was telling me
that when he was a kid,
his parents used to have loud sex,
like all the time.
And they would leave their door open.
And he would then stand
outside their door
and just watch his dad
go to town on his mom.
What the fuck?
Holy shit.
And it would make Gary feel
this mixture of, like,
disgust and jealousy,
but at the same time, excitement.
You know? Like, his heart was racing.
And then, when he got older
and started dating,
he would have these paranoid delusions
that his girlfriend
would be cheating on him
with his best friend, and he'd obsess,
even though there was no basis
for it in reality.
And he would have these jealous rages,
and, I mean, he lost
a lot of friends over it.
Yeah, I'm sure he did.
And one day, he realized
he kind of hoped
they were having sex behind his back.
So, he could find them doing it.
Just like he found his parents doing it
in the middle of the night.
So, it's kind of like
his worst nightmare
was actually his erotic fantasy.
Okay, that is demented.
No, I'm glad he told me.
So, what do you think?
About what?
Helping Gary.
Helping Gary how?
Well, staying and...
you know.
What? No. What? No.
Oh, relax. He wouldn't even touch you.
He just wants to creep up on us.
And at some point, I'll leave you,
and I'll go to Gary.
And it would be like
he's winning his mother back
from his father.
Yeah, like a little boy's dream.
What, are you both insane?
Come on. I really want
this relationship to work.
- Please help.
- How?
- By boning you in front of him?
- Yes.
No.
What? No, no.
I am not that kind of guy. No.
Uh, yeah, you are.
I gotta go. I'll see you guys later.
I'm sorry, babe.
Whatever.
Okay, well, I'm gonna go. Love you.
All right. We're good.
- All right, well...
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- You want this?
- No, man.
You said you weren't gonna bring that.
Yeah, I lied. I'm sorry.
What happened, man? You okay?
Yeah.
I... I built this guy up
in my... my mind
to be this thing.
And I'm sitting there,
and I'm looking at him,
and he's just this pathetic,
frail, old man.
I mean, I couldn't even hit him.
So, you got some closure?
Yeah. Yeah.
That's a huge monkey off your back.
- You feel good?
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
- Let's get a drink.
- Really?
Let's celebrate. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Come on. Let's go.
- I thought you... you're...
you're sober, though, right?
You don't want...
Sober? That ship sailed.
Come on. Let's go big.
You think it's a good idea?
We're in Bangkok, man. Let's fucking go.
- One night.
- All right.
I'll go back to the monastery tomorrow.
Paint this town red.
Get a bucket, splash it around.
Are you crazy? Take the money.
If I did that,
I'd be an accomplice to murder.
No... No, you wouldn't.
He's buying me off
so I don't tell anyone where he is.
Okay, so let him buy you off then.
It's not right, Zion. He had her killed.
Look, Ma, 100,000 dollars
is a lot of money.
Come on, you could take
the whole year off.
I'm not doing it, Zion. I'm... I'm not.
Okay, Ma. If you don't come
to terms with him,
he's gonna come after you.
You know that, right?
And they're gonna find your body
in the Gulf of Thailand.
Shit, maybe mine, too.
Can't I get one fucking break
this fucking lifetime?
- Hey.
- Hi.
Laurie's not responding to my texts.
She'll get over it.
Okay.
What?
I just... You know,
I... I feel bad, but I guess,
you know, you don't, so...
How bad am I supposed to feel?
You don't know my situation, okay?
I'm... I'm not judging you, Jac.
I was actually defending you at dinner.
Whatever.
It's fine. I'll be the, uh...
I'll be the bad guy. I'm used to it.
Okay, well...
that's a good night.
- Night.
You know, you have the wrong impression
of me, right?
Do I?
Yeah. I mean, I'm not just one thing.
I mean, I could be
somebody else if I wanted.
Well, then I think you should.
I mean, I bet I could even connect
with you on a spiritual level,
since that's so important to you.
What?
No, try me.
You know, teach me your ways.
If you want to develop spiritually,
you have to learn to meditate.
So, focus on your breathing.
Okay, so the most important thing
is to take everything very slow.
Just clear your mind of everything else.
Yeah. So you get the idea. Yeah?
What, that's it?
You can't become soulful
in ten minutes. It takes time.
I'll give you some books.
These are really good.
She's a genius. She'll change your life,
but you've gotta go.
I've gotta call Rick.
I'm really worried about him.
Your call
has been forwarded to voicemail.
The person you're try...
What you doing?
I'm praying for Piper
to be miserable in that temple tonight.
Maybe Jesus will save her
from those Buddhists.
Oh, God.
Oh.
So, you, uh,
you live in New York City, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
- So cool.
- I've always wanted to go.
- Yeah?
Yeah. It's my dream.
Well, let me know if you do.
It'd be fun to take you around.
- Hmm. What?
- Although, um...
if I ever leave this country,
they won't let me back in.
I've overstayed my visa.
I need to go back home
to Vladivostok to get my mother,
but I can't.
- Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
- Yeah.
My poor mother.
She's sick and old.
Oh.
I need...
ten thousand US dollars
to pay off her debts
and buy her plane ticket.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
Can you help me?
Oh.
- Yeah.
- I... I wish I could.
I know you're rich.
Oh, no, no. I'm not that rich.
Please, my mother needs me.
She'll die there.
Uh... I... I... I don't have
that kind of money on me. It's...
You could wire it.
Wire it?
You have PayPal? Or Zelle?
- Uh...
- I really need help.
Cash App?
Uh...
I'm sorry to ask.
I don't know what else to do.
No, no.
I... I'm not rich...
Lyosha!
What the... What?
Quiet. I'll handle it.
Hey, hey, Nadya! Spokoyno!
Where is your little bitch?
Laurie, come back! We'll talk about it!
- Oh, look at this. Wait a minute. Wait.
- Oh!
Whoa, whoa, look at that.
Quick little...
Whoa. Hey. All right. Here we go.
It's a party now!
I just don't think at this age
I'm meant to live
an uncomfortable life.
Honestly, I don't know
if I'd want to live.
I don't have
anything else but this.
If I'm not a success, then I'm nothing.
And I can't handle being nothing.
I'm sorry.
sync and corrections by solfieri
www.MY-SUBS.com